Finding Aid for the Benjamin Aaron Papers LSC.0413
UCLA Library Special Collections
- The Labor Board at Mid-Century Rights of Individual Employees Washington, D.C., 1985 Oct 2-4 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Manuscripts, Publications and Reports (Box 36, Folder 4-7)
- Wrongful Termination Project, Miscellaneous Materials (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Wrongful Termination Project, 1983-1984 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Materials on Plant Closures and Removals (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Comparative Labor Law: Payments, Deposits, Monthly Financial Reports, 1983-1986 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- ILO Statements (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Southwestern Legal Foundation: General, 1967-1968 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- TAPILS (Box 36, Folder 14)
- ILO Reports of U.S. Delegation (Box 36, Folder 15)
- ILO Correspondence, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- BA's Memoir Outline (Box 37, Folder 2)
- The ILO Committee of Experts, 1985-1994 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- The National Academy of Arbitrators, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Comparative Labor Law Group, 1966-1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- The International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- The Labor Law Group, 1947-1985 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Los Angeles Mayor's Labor Management Advisory Committee, 1974-1978 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- California Assembly Advisory Council on Public Employee Relations, 1972-1973 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- The Joint Committee on Public Employer-Employee Relations, California Legislature, 1974 Dec 1-1975 Jun 30 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Los Angeles County Employee Relations Ordinance, 1968-1972 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Los Angeles School Teachers' Strike, 1970 Apr-May (Box 37, Folder 12)
- California Farm Labor Panel, 1965 Apr-Dec (Box 37, Folder 13)
- National Commission Technology, Automation, and Economic Progress, 1964-1966 (Box 37, Folder 14)
- Memoirs: Emergency Disputes, 1960-1992 (Box 37, Folder 15)
- Memoirs: National Wage Stabilization Board, 1951-1952 (Box 37, Folder 16)
- Memoirs: Labor Advisory Mission - Japan, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 17)
- Memoirs: National War Labor Board, 1942-1945 (Box 37, Folder 18)
- Benjamin Aaron Memoirs - Comments on Drafts (Box 37, Folder 19)
- The United Auto Workers Public Review Board, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 20)
- IRAA "Distinguished Panel" Chicago, Jan 1998 (Box 37, Folder 21)
- Arbitration Board No. 282 BRT vs. Richmond, Friedricksberg, & Potomac RR (Box 37, Folder 22)
- Arbitration Board 282, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 23)
- Canadian Task Force on Labor Relations (Box 37, Folder 24)
- Engineers and Technicians in the Southern California Airframe Industry, 1953 (Box 37, Folder 25)
- Correspondence (Box 37, Folder 26)
- ABA Labor & Employment Law Section Conference on Personal Rights in the Workplace, 1981 Apr 30 (Box 37, Folder 27)
- Board No. 282 - Carriers Represented by: Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers: Conf. Committees and BLE, BLF&E, ORC&B, BRT, and SUNA (Box 37, Folder 28)
- Tribute to Gino Giugni, 2007 Apr (Box 37, Folder 29)
- Conference on the Past and Future of Comparative Labor Law, 2005 Oct 7-9 (Box 37, Folder 30)
- "POWER" (Box 37, Folder 31)
- John Randolph Tucker lecture, 1982 May 8 (Box 37, Folder 32)
- IRAA Special Research Volume, 1971; Public Policy and Labor-Management Relations (Box 37, Folder 33)
- Public Review Board International Union, UAW (Box 38, Folder 1)
- The National Academy of Arbitrators 2005 Annual Meeting (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Coordinating Committee Steel Companies and United Steelworkers of America, 1983 July 27-31 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- ISLLSS - Second European Regional Congress - Jesolo, Italy, 1986 Sep 8-10 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1982 Oct-Dec (Box 38, Folder 5)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1983 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- ISLLSS - European Congress (Szeged) (Box 38, Folder 7)
- ISLLSS - Fourth Asian Regional Congress - Singapore, 1987 Feb 3-6 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1984 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security (Box 38, Folder 10)
- ISLLSS - XII World Congress Madrid, 1988 Sep 20-23 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- ISLLSS - First American Regional Congress - Buenos Aires, 1987 Apr 23-30 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Legislation (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Otto Kahn-Freund (Box 38, Folder 14)
- UAW Public Review Board (Box 38, Folder 15)
- UAW Public Review Board, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 16-17)
- UAW Public Review Board Decision Nos. 1391-1399 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board, 1960 Apr 22 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board, 1992 May 28 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- First Annual US Mexico International Labor Law Conference, 1992 Oct 25-27 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Grodin Article Draft of Gilmer Arbitration (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Dunlop Commission Report (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Governmental Regulation of Internal Union Affairs - Australia (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Our Economic System: Its Strengths and Weaknesses, 1989 Nov 13 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Manuscripts, articles, journals and correspondence (Box 39, Folder 6-14)
  Bulk of the materials include Aaron's annotated manuscript drafts, "Union Security in Australia and the United States" and related research materials.
- Japan International Labor Law Forum, 1996 Mar (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Howard Block Arbitration Decisions - Hawaiian Airlines & ALPA (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Internal Union Affairs - Canada (Box 40, Folder 3)
- International Encyclopedia of Comparative Law - materials (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Comparative Labor Law Miscellaneous Materials (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Correspondence (Box 40, Folder 6)
  Letter from Frank W. McCulloch concerning the AFL-CIO with related ILO and ILC documents.
- Internal Union Affairs - Australia (Box 40, Folder 7)
- 260. Labor Law I Spring, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Labor Law Courses, 1967-1986 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- UCLA Faculty Welfare Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- CUCEA, 1995-1996 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- UCLA Emeriti Association General Economic Welfare Committee (Box 40, Folder 12)
- UCLA Emeriti Assn. - Nominations Comm. (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Emeriti Parking Steering Committee (Box 40, Folder 14)
- UCLA Emeriti Association - Awards Committee (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Panunzio Distinguished Emeriti Award (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Emeriti Directory (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Labor Law Group, 2000 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Labor Law Group Trust, 1979-1984 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Labor Law Group, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Labor Law Group, 1975-1978 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Issues under NAFTA (Box 41, Folder 5)
- NAFTA Labor Side Agreement Seminar on NAO Submission No. 9601, 1997 Dec 4 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Conference on the Role of the New NAFTA Institutions, 1998 June 19-20 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- NAFTA clippings (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Labor Law in Mexico (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Resumes, Biographies, Bibliographies and Salary Correspondence (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Benjamin Aaron, 1974 Oct 31 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  Aaron's "Comments on Staff Recommendations to Joint Committee on Postsecondary Education re Collective Bargaining in Postsecondary Education and correspondence from the California Legislature Joint Committee on Postsecondary Education.
- American Arbitration Association, 1974 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- International Society for Labor and Social Security Law, 2000-2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security, 1995-1999 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security Circular Letters, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security Circular Letters, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Johannes Schregle Confidential Correspondence (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Dean Selection Committee, 1969, 1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Employer Promulgated Arbitration (Box 42, Folder 7)
- ILLR - S.CT. Cases (Box 42, Folder 8)
- International Labor Law Reports, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- International Labor Law Reports, 1991-1999 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Appraisal of Grant Applications and Letters of Reference (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Stenographic Transcript of Hearings Before the Committee of Education and Labor House of Representatives, 1952 June 3 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Resumes (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Farm Labor Legislation (Box 43, Folder 4)
- 21st Annual Southwest Labor Studies Association Conference, 1995 May 4-6 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Ellen Dannin - Fulbright Application (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Employee Voice: A Legal Perspective, 1992 Jan 4 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Structural Development of Worker Participation in Sweden (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Industrial Relations in Western Europe (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Racial Discrimination in Employment (Box 43, Folder 10)
- International Labour Organization (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Workshop on Labor and Employment Law, 1992 April 9-11 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Comparative Labor Law and Labor Movements (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous Speeches and Articles (Box 43, Folder 14)
- National Mediation Board Emergency Boards 220, 221 and 222 General File (Box 43, Folder 15)
- Emergency Boards No. 220, 221 and 222 (Box 43, Folder 16)
- Emergency Labor Dispute Task Force, 1966 (Box 43, Folder 17)
- Material on Railway Labor Act (Box 43, Folder 18)
- Labor Relations in Rail & Air Transport Industries (Box 43, Folder 19)
- Material on National Emergency Disputes (Box 43, Folder 20)
- Comparative Labor Law Group: Strikes and Lockouts - Notes and Memoranda (Box 43, Folder 21)
- Final Report of the California Farm Panel, 1965 Dec 1 (Box 43, Folder 22)
- NAA Book: Common Law of the Workplace (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Tribute to Mel Reich, 2000 Mar 11 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Labor Arbitration After WWII: The Southern California Story (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Irving Bernstein, 1916-2001 Obituary and Remembrance (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Tribute to Ted St. Antoine, 1998 Apr 15 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Studi Sul Lavoro in Honor of Gino Giugni, 1998 July 31 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Tribute to David Suskind, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Liber Amicorum Roger Blanpain (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Remembering the 1970 Los Angeles Teachers' Strike, 2002 Oct 14 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- B. Aaron - Oral History, 1996-1999 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Union Mergers and Affiliations (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Mass Layoffs - US (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Warn Act (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Labor Law Group. Scottsdale Conference, 1999 Dec 9-10 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Regulating Mass Layoffs/Collective Redundancies in the United States and the European Union (Liber Amicorum in Honor of Max Rood), 1996 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- NAA Fall Education Conference - 1997 Nashville, TN (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Book Review, European Community Labor Law/Principles and Perspectives (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Trip to Japan, 1996 Nov (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Book Review, The ILO/The International Standards System and Basic Human Rights, Bartolomei, Von Potobsky & Swepston (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Book Review, Human Rights and Labor Law, Essays for Paul O'Higgins Comparative Labor Law Journal, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Commission for Labor Cooperation (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Erasmus University Rotterdam Research Project (Box 44, Folder 22)
- European Trip, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- ISLLSS Labor Law Congress 2002 Stockholm, 2002 Sep 4-6 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- XVI World Congress, ISLLSS Jerusalem, Israel, 2000 Sep 3-7 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- VI European Congress ISLLSS Warsaw, Poland, 1999 Sep 13-17 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- 5th European Regional Congress ISLLSS Leiden, the Netherlands, 1996 Sep 17-21 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- International Society for Labor Law and Social Security 6th Asian Regional Congress Hobart, Tasmania, 1996 Feb 12-15 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- NAA Continuing Education Conference, 1990 Nov 1-4 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- NAA Continuing Education Conference - Ottawa, 1991 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- NAA Fall Education Conference, 1994 (Box 44, Folder 31)
- NAA Fall Education Conference, 1995 (Box 44, Folder 32)
- NAA Fall Education Conference, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 33)
- NAA Committee on International Studies, 1992-1999 (Box 44, Folder 34)
- Southwestern Legal Foundation Short Course: Labor Disputes Settlement, 1977 Mar 14-17 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- League of Women Voters - Symposium on Public-Sector Collective Bargaining, 1977 Feb 15 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- ABA National Institute on Labor Relations Law in the Public Sector, 1976 Nov 18-19 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Educational Employment Relations - Grievance and Arbitrations, 1976 Jun 29-30 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Speech to IRRA on Collective Bargaining in the Public Sector. Denver, 1976 May 7 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- National Academy of Arbitrators - Annual Meeting, 1976 Apr 23 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Southwestern Legal Foundation Short Course-Dispute Settlement, 1976 Mar 15-17 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Conference on Fundamental Job Rights of Public Employees, 1976 Feb 6 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Collective Bargaining Conference, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Conference on Comparative Aspects of Industrial Conflict University of Toronto, 1975 Apr 3-4 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Conference on Swedish Collective Bargaining Law, 1975 Oct 8-9 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Conference with Swedish Representatives, 1974 Oct 7 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Address: 47th Annual Conference of Arizona Cities and Towns - Tucson, 1974 Oct 10 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- NCDS Reginal Seminar, Las Vegas, 1974 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- "Arbitrators and Professional Responsibility" Address Presented at IRR Conference on "The Public Interest and the Arbitrator", 1974 Feb 20 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Joint Meeting, IRRA & IRR Alumni Association, 1974 Feb 13 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Address: The Role of Arbitrators in Claims of Discrimination Because of Race, Religion, or Sex - and the Parties' Views IRRA - New York Chapter, 1972 May 18 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Trade Union Fellows (Box 45, Folder 18)
- The Making of the Model Employment Termination Act (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Janice R. Bellace (Box 45, Folder 20)
- United Nations Association of the US (Box 45, Folder 21)
- David Thagman (Box 45, Folder 22)
- NAFTA: Pitfalls and Possibilities UCLA, 1993 Nov 5 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- University Administrative Matters (Box 45, Folder 24)
- American Academy of Arts and Sciences - Western Center Interdisciplinary Study Project, 1995 (Box 45, Folder 25)
- National Research Council Transportation Research Board (Box 45, Folder 26)
- International Termination of Contract (Box 45, Folder 27)
- United Airlines Inc. "Mock" Hearing, 1996 Aug 22-23 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Industrial Relations Europe, 1985 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Issues and Dilemmas in the Arbitration of Claims under Wrongful Dismissal Legislation and Other Forms of Non-Union Arbitration (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Developments in Arbitration for Underrepresented Employees: What, Why and Whither, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Statutory Discrimination Claims: Rights Waived and Lost in the Arbitration Forum, 1996 (Box 45, Folder 32)
- Executive Order No. 12954 (Striker Replacements), 1995 (Box 45, Folder 33)
- Governmental Regulation of Union Internal Affairs in Australia and The United States manuscript (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Governmental Regulation of Union Internal Affairs in Australia and The United States notes (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Johannes Schegle (Box 46, Folder 3)
- United States Bankruptcy Courts Southern District of New York (Box 46, Folder 4)
- George Strauss Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 5)
- NAO Submission 94003 (Sony) (Box 46, Folder 6)
- David Mellinkoff Memorial (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Lawrence Hearing Health Care Inc. Hearing Aids (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Jesse Dukeminier Memorial Entry (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Arbitration of Employment Disputes Outside the Collective Bargaining Structure, LA County BAR Assoc., 1995 Sep 20 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- UPS - Teamsters Labor Dispute (Box 46, Folder 11)
- National Academy of Arbitrators - History (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Los Angeles Board of Civil Service Commissioners Hearing Officer File, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Labor Law Group Conference, 1995 Dec 7-10 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Appraisal of Davies Freedland and Sciarra Employment Policy and the Regulation of Part-time work in the EU: A Comparative Analysis (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Shiva Falsafi (Box 46, Folder 16)
- David Mellinkoff Memorial Lecture Series (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Code of International Labour Law - Neville Rubin, et al. (Box 46, Folder 18)
- ABA Section of Labor and Employment Law Luncheon Speech San Francisco, 1997 Aug 5 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Institute on the Law of Work (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Evaluation for Marley Weiss for Promotion to Full Professor (Box 46, Folder 21)
- University Emeriti & Pre-Retirement Relations Committee, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- UCLA Emeriti Association, 1994-1996 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Materials on Sexual Harassment (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Individual Employment Rights in Labor Law Curriculum (Box 47, Folder 4)
- UCLA IIR Conference on Concession Bargaining, 1984 Mar 13 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Conference on the Duty of Fair Representation Revisited, 1983 Oct 20-21 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- First Oxford/BNA Symposium on Comparative Industrial Relations, 1983 Aug 3-17 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Labor-Management Arbitration Conference, Anaheim CA, 1983 Mar 17 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Conference on the Future of the US Industrial Relations System Berkeley, 1982 Oct 8-9 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Conference on Legal Aspects of Union Relations, Anaheim, 1982 Oct 25 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Role of the Arbitrator in Insuring a Fair Hearing, 1982 May 27 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Arbitration and the Duty of Fair Representation - ABA Comm. On Arbitration, 1981 Feb 9 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Ownership of Jobs: Observations on the American Experience, 1981 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Third Asian Regional Congress ISLLSS, Bangkok, Thailand, 1985 Jan 8-11 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Second Asian Congress on Labor Law and Social Security Seoul, S. Korea, 1983 Sep 14-16 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- First Asian Congress on Labor Law and Social Security, 1980 Dec 12-16 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Conference on Protection Against Unjust Discharge MSU, 1980 Sep 28-30 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Symposium on New Developments on Labor Law Teaching and Research, 1980 Sep 27-29 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Administrative Law Judges Conference, 1980 Feb 7 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Arbitration Decisions and the Law of the Shop - IRRA Spring Meeting, 1978 May 13 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- University of Toronto, Centre for Industrial Relations, 1979 Mar 29 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Right of Workers to Organize - US (Box 47, Folder 22)
- U of Ariz. Fourteenth Annual Lab. Law Conf., Tucson, Ariz., 1978 Feb 16 (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Pending Arbitration Matters (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Ansett Airlines (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Bellagio Hotel and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (David Wagner), 2004 Apr (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Bellagio Hotel and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (Russel Bennett), 2004 Feb 11 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Bellagio Hotel and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (Marla Manett) (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Banks v. Bethlehem Steel Corporation, 1990 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- City of Los Angeles, Board of Civil Service Commissions (Discharge of Carlo Chaingan), 2005 Jan 27 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- City of Los Angeles, Board of Civil Service Commissioners (Discharge of Claude Soucy), 2004 Mar 9 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Eastern Airlines and Dist. 100, IAMAW, 1982-1987 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Eastern Airlines and TWUA (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Eastern Airlines Arbitration Decisions (Non-Represented Employees) (Box 48, Folder 11)
- El Cortez Hotel and Casino and Culinary Workers Union, Local 226 (Judith Wohlheiter), 1993 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Excalibur and Bartenders Union, Local 165 (Roger Davis), 1995 Jan 13 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Fox Television Stations Inc. and AFTRA. Case No. 72 300 00232 93 (Overtime Pay), 1994 Mar 28 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Fremont Hotel and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (Mary Saulter), 2003 June 24 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Fremont Hotel and Casino and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (Sarah Bennett), 1997 Apr 17 (Box 48, Folder 16)
- Fremont Hotel and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (Rhonda Howes), 1994 Sep 20 (Box 48, Folder 17)
- Fremont Hotel and Casino and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (Padro Felix), 1993 Apr 5 (Box 48, Folder 18)
- Frontier Airlines and IAMAW (Box 48, Folder 19)
- General Electric Co. and IUERMW, 1984, 1987-1988 (Box 48, Folder 20)
- GTE and CWA Grievance #GCM-4056 (Gregory James) (Box 48, Folder 21)
- GTE and CWA, 1993 Oct (Box 48, Folder 22)
- GTE California Inc. and CWA, 1988-1990 (Box 48, Folder 23)
- Golden Gate Casino and Culinary Workers, Local 226 (James Jones), 2002 Jun 13 (Box 48, Folder 24)
- Greyhound Lines, Inc. and ATU (Telephone Information Center), 1986 May 15 (Box 48, Folder 25)
- Greyhound Lines, Inc. and Amalgamated Council and ATU Decisions, 1980-1994 (Box 48, Folder 26)
- Hawaiian Airlines and ALPA HAL-13-00GG, 2000 Jul 20 (Box 48, Folder 27)
- Hawaiian Airlines and ALPA Case No. HAL68-98GG (Box 48, Folder 28)
- Hawaiian Airlines and ALPA HAL7-97GG (Deadhead seating), 1997 June (Box 48, Folder 29)
- Hawaiian Airlines Inc. and ALPA Decisions and Opinions, 1991 (Box 48, Folder 30)
- Hawaiian Airlines and ALPA General File (Box 48, Folder 31)
- Holiday Inn on the Bay and HERE, Local 30 San Diego, CA, 2003 Aug 28 (Box 48, Folder 32)
- Horseshoe Hotel and Casino and Culinary Workers Union, Local 226 (Glover and Jackson), 1993 (Box 48, Folder 33)
- Housing Authority of City of LA and LA Building Trades Council Case No. 72 4J0 00004 94, 1994 June 7 (Box 48, Folder 34)
- Arb. Hughes Airwest and Local No. 32 Aircraft Mechs Fraternal Assn. Grievances, 1976 (Box 48, Folder 35)
- IBEW Local 21 SBC Midwest Downers Grove, IL, 2005 Jul 12 (Box 48, Folder 36)
- IBEW Local 18 and LA Department of Water and power (George Allers) Arb. 228, 1982 (Box 48, Folder 37)
- Inland Container Corp. and United paper Workers Int'l Union, Local No. 961 Case No. 72 300 0230 90, 1990 Oct 11 (Box 48, Folder 38)
- James Jones Company and Glass MPP & AW-No. 72 300 0307 91, 1992 Apr 14 (Box 48, Folder 39)
- Arb. Japan Airlines and IAM, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 40)
- JWR Construction Inc. and UMWA, District 22, 1998 June 23 (Box 48, Folder 41)
- Railway Labor Act (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Enforcement of Collective Agreements (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Union Unfair Labor Practices Under Sections 8(B) (1), (2), (3) of the NLRA (Box 49, Folder 3)
- National Advisory Panel for American Justice Institute Study of Labor Relations in Correctional Agencies, 1975-1976 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Collective Bargaining and the Anti-Trust Laws (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Employers and Union Conduct Affecting the Establishment of Collective Bargaining (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Establishing Collective Agreements (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Duty to Bargain Collectively (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Arbitration and the NLRB (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Preemption (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Material on Labor Courts (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Labor Law Short Course Discrimination in Employment (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Canadian Royal Commission Inquiry into Labor Disputes (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Labor Law Notes, 1939-1942 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- National Academy of Arbitrators Special Committee on Development of New Arbitrators (Box 49, Folder 15)
- AAA - Employment Law Subcommittee (Box 49, Folder 16)
- George A. Daniels and California Portland Cement Co. Case No. 72 116 0491 84, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- George A. Daniels and California Portland Cement Co. Case No. 72 116 0491 84, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Major League Baseball Player Arbitration, 1982 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Arb. Coordinating Committee Steel Companies and United Steel Workers, 1978 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Kalitta Air and Teamsters Local 747 (Dan Criss, et al., Grievance No. 2-0 30-829, Ypsilanti, MI), 2005 Oct 26-27 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Kerr Glass Co. and GBBA Grievance No. 81-21-15 (Subcontracting), 1982 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Las Vegas Valley Water Dist and Water Employees Ass'n (R. White and R. Summers), 1987 May 13 (Box 50, Folder 3)